my will made real Maura is here oh it is
not my preference to see to matters
personally but I will see them done I'm
not dead yet
perhaps a new methodology is required
evolution works quickly today it seems
likely the enemy is using a teleporter
enemy turret is no more I feel
unstoppable take cover
I need assistance help me I believe we
need another healer enemy turret within
my sight I feel unwell we must defend
our objective against their attacks
they're making gains
we must limit them to our benefit my
power grows hahaha some bruh is that you
an expedient solution
I admire your efficacy yell are there my
condition is improved I have located the
teleporter thank you
I must know how your technology
functions my power is overwhelming I
have destroyed the enemy's teleporter
sniper we must be cautious the enemy
gathers here they're taking the
objective the payload moves with
certainty why we stopped behind you a
touch from afar I cast this forth
someone is hiding here the enemy's
shield generator has been destroyed I
have found the enemy's shield generator
I believe the enemy has a shield
generator our time runs short we must
increase our efforts slowly they realize
that failure is all that awaits them my
just rewards I agree with your
assessment too close for comfort my
knowledge grows they are above us
they're attacking from behind the enemy
is below us watch the doorway
they're coming directly at us enemy on
our left the enemy is on our right much
obliged
we must halt the payload stop the pail
Oh
I could use some shields knowledge is
its own reward
I heard you understood get in there
after you defend the objective move here
if you wish to be healed join with me
hello there I'm over here I'm right here
I'm without armor
I require healing I am in need of
shields group up we must eliminate the
objective I understand I'm in need of
armor
we need a healer I need healing I'm on
my way
push forward we need to move the payload
move the payload we must recover our
flag recover the flag ready I am ready
let's make our preparations here setup
here thank you you have my thanks
my ultimate is almost charged
coalescence is almost ready
my ultimate ability is charging
coalescence is charging my ultimate is
ready to be unleashed I am ready to
unleash coalescence coalescence is ready
advance with me I'm with you by your
side no incoming get ready
prepare yourself I'm on the attack
attack the objective take the objective
the area five four three two one in five
four three two one
capture the flag we must capture the
flag defend our flag defend the flag
move into defense defend the objective
we must protect the objective fall back
find their teleporter go goodbye
farewell
Eradicator eliminated leaving the flag
here no trooper down I'm on fire all
evidence supports this claim I will not
be denied
detonator inbound your involvement in my
research is at an end our objective has
been damaged
a welcome improvement
myself no support story of my life the
objective has been eliminated
do not lose focus now victory is near
our efforts draw to a close concentrate
our efforts on the objective gather at
the objective the objectives been
damaged the enemy approaches on the
right watch our left side they advance
straight at us mind the doorway move the
objective forward damage levels on our
objective are critical brilliant always
with a touch of the dramatic the enemy
has been eliminated the odds have
shifted in our favor a significant
amount of data to analyze harridan our
guardian angel an unwelcome interruption
we must make haste our time grows short
we must take control of the objective
capture the objective our defenses have
been breached the process begins again
you're a chancer I am restored
sláinte I'm working one hand gives the
other takes away we learn from failure
not from success despair has its own
comes what for enemies below us enemies
to our rear when faced with a setback we
must challenge our assumptions I will
rebuild you Vanek thena Fela porrik
science will reveal the truth
Korean Bert broher it's been bail in a
host thank you for your contributions
better living through science eeeh Hana
Hana ditch Moira by her side I've cited
the enemy I must reflect upon this
guinea pigs a small loss what are you on
about
evolutionary dead end I will allow none
to stand in the way of progress this was
the expected conclusion was the outcome
ever in doubt
I've relinquished the flag let's not
allow this to become a habit an
undesirable outcome someone recover the
flag our flag is free pure class to be
expected impeccable
do not underestimate me this was the
only plausible outcome huh your strength
herbs your power is mine such a flawed
creation that's much better
I am not finished with you yet your
strength fades I will draw the strength
from your body perhaps next time you
should not stand in the way of the orb
huh I am optimized strength flows from
you get into position regenerating your
cellular structure this will improve
your condition
we're still within the margin of error
huh hmm
affective find their weakness and claim
the objective if we are to progress we
must claim the objective the payload
moves towards our desired outcome we
must ensure the payloads progress the
payload has been stopped we must get it
moving again we must come together
before we can continue detonator
destroyed enemy bastion destroyed escort
the objective so our fourteen destroyed
slicer destroyed enemy bastion engaging
Eradicator engaging no trooper sighted
so our 14 approaching slicer is coming
for us
the enemy is placed a turret here the
government here has such a medieval view
towards on Nick's thoughts our Hulagu
bershka shin shin shin i need to be
revived i need to be healed
i'm seriously injured a dreamer is one
who can only find his way by moonlight
and his punishment is that he sees the
dawn before the rest of the world we are
all in the gutter but some of us are
looking at the Stars
Darius what an interesting hypothesis
stupidity is not a right performance
enhanced Nullah kana did
how are you feeling Lacroix toy tempered
an art gan wha
who Garos Margit I'm going in come to me
and I will heal you come here for
healing group up with me hello greetings
eliminate the target yes there was a
flaw in my approach what time we had is
fading our inevitable victory beckons
their inevitable defeat is becoming
reality you have served your purpose are
you finished something is amiss your
body decays predictable the state of you
calm yourself unsightly they made it
easy from me my keen analytical mind
detects a pattern forming press the
attack
I'm on fire you'd be wise to stay out of
my sight this is now my home as much as
any other if only the world could see
the wonders that science has built it
was inevitable we must recover our flag
they have our flag we must take it back
I will see the flag safely back to base
I am taking possession of the flag it
was only to be expected dispatching the
flag to base ha ha ha the true struggle
is for the superiority of ideas
returning the flag to base more you grow
weak surrender to my will this will heal
you allow me to repair the damage your
assistance is appreciated situational
awareness could save your life
I recommend it huh simple geometry right
where I wanted you
affective positioning the power of
destruction yes this is my will
gone swiftly repairing the damaged
science saves the day again
injured again your injuries are
fascinating restoring you allow me how
conveniently arranged this will restore
you furious meet at the objective
eliminate the objective the target is
dead we must all make sacrifices in the
name of science
this objective must be ours it appears
we have suffered a minor setback your
ignorance frightens me you've made a
dog's breakfast of it the enemy is
laying claim to our objective our our
enemies believe that they can take our
objective they are mistaken
that we should fail in stopping the
payload has no reasonable explanation we
must keep our enemies from further
progress towards their goal your
contributions to the furtherance of
science are to be commended as expected
Grand those who wronged me pay in the
end
remember the favor I have done for you
this day you can repay me later our
enemies return an ominous portent the
objective is almost destroyed it all
comes down to this prepare yourselves
for the decisive battle victory is
within our grasp let us go on to the end
we must reverse the course that we are
on another setback and all will be lost
our enemies are above us our objective
is almost destroyed reaction 'got sure
hey Mahal Gaurav Maha got we need to
bring our ally back into the fight our
ally needs to be revived revive me no my
yes victim kuru lot your contributions
are still required we must attack defend
with me slowly Walia sloan absolute zero
ishka the best mistake one could ever
make
Gail DOMA ho idle hands are the devil's
workshop biologies habits are hard to
break
toi mala Jota time the dalish joinder
the Yeshu me love weakness toy guy riga
golem
is my thinking tell me how this feels no
need to mess about
hurry up without us
Oh
uh-huh uh-huh I will unmake you
you seem in need of aid I'm restoring
you
[Music]